Historical Photograph Collection: Glass-Plate Negatives Series, 1880-1920: Preliminary Finding Aid AC317
University Archives
- Athletics, 1881-1938; 51 boxes
  - Crew, 1913-1920; 7 boxes
    - Crew on lake, Undated; 1 box (Box 11)
      Plate number: 276
    - Crew, 1913, 1 box (Box 22)
      Plate number: 365
    - Crowd going down to Carnegie Lake for Cornell Princeton race in May, 1919, 1 box (Box 32)
      Original sleeve No. 114
      Plate number: 645
    - Fall regatta on Carnegie Lake, 1919, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 192-193
      Plate number: 724-725
    - Princeton defeating Cornell on Carnegie Lake, by half a length, 1919, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 194
      Plate number: 726
    - Crowd on bank at Princeton v. Cornell race, May, 1919, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 195
      Plate number: 727
    - Professor Spaeth on the launch, at the Cornell race, 1919, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 196
      Plate number: 728
    - Child's Cup race on Carnegie Lake, 1918, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 197
      Plate number: 729
    - Cornell freshmen beating Princeton freshmen, 1919, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 199
      Plate number: 731
    - The Navy defeating Princeton in the Child's Cup race on the Schuylkill River, 1920, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 200
      Plate number: 732
    - Princeton leading Penn at the finish of the Child's Cup race on the Schuylkill River, 1920, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 201
      Plate number: 733
    - The Navy, Princeton, Penn and Columbia coming down the Schuylkill River in the Child's Cup race, 1920, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 202
      Plate number: 734
    - Crew race in fall regatta, 1919, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 198
      Plate number: 730
    - Navy, Syracuse and Princeton coming down the river in the American Henley at Philadelphia, 1920, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 203
      Plate number: 735
    - Navy, Syracuse and Princeton approaching the finish in the American Henley at Philadelphia, 1920, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 204
      Plate number: 736
    - The Navy beating Syracuse and Princeton in the American Henley, Philadelphia, 1920, 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 299
      Plate number: 794
    - Crew crossing finish line on Carnegie Lake, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1047
      Plate number: 1053
    - Princeton varsity crew, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1048
      Plate number: 1054
    - Princeton varsity crew on the lake, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1049
      Plate number: 1055
    - 1921 Freshman crew, 1917, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1050
      Plate number: 1056
    - Close finish of Cornell race, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1051
      Plate number: 1057
    - Athletics, crew on machines in gym, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1234
    - Athletics, crew - 1918 on rowing machines in gym, Dec. 1914, 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1235
    - Athletics, crew on lake, 1915, 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1236
    - Athletics, crew on lake near boathouse, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1237
    - Athletics, 1918 crew squad in front of boat house, circa 1918; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1238
    - Athletics, crew - Columbia supporters Carnegie Lake, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1239
    - Athletics, crew - launch at Childs Cup Race, Coach Nicholls of Pennsylvania and Coach Rice of Columbia seated, Dr. Spaeth standing, Lake Carnegie, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1240
  - Football, 1881-1934; 10 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture the Princeton University Football team.
    - Football scrub team, 1892, 1 box (Box 22)
      Plate number: 366
    - Football team, 1896, 1 box (Box 22)
      Plate number: 367-368
    - Football team, Undated; 1 box (Box 22)
      Plate number: 369
    - Football practice on University Field, 1920, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 205
      Plate number: 737
    - Football practice on University Field, 1919, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 206-207
      Plate number: 738-739
    - Jack Strubing, quarterback of 1919 team, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 208
      Plate number: 740
    - Coaches of 1919 team, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 209. Nat Poe, Keene Fitzpatrick, Bill Roper, and Ballin
      Plate number: 741
    - Trimble's Touchdown in the Harvard-Princeton game, 1919, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 210
      Plate number: 742
    - Left section of Panorama of Palmer Stadium during Harvard-Princeton game, 1919, 1 box (Box 37)
      Original sleeve No. 211
      Plate number: 743
    - Left-center section of panorama of Palmer Stadium during Harvard-Princeton game, 1919, 1 box (Box 38)
      Original sleeve No. 212
      Plate number: 744
    - Right-center section of panorama of Palmer Stadium during Harvard-Princeton game, 1919, 1 box (Box 38)
      Original sleeve No. 213
      Plate number: 745
    - Right section of panorama of Palmer Stadium during Harvard-Princeton game, 1919, 1 box (Box 38)
      Original sleeve No. 214
      Plate number: 746
    - Left section of panorama of Yale Bowl during Yale-Princeton game, 1919, 1 box (Box 38)
      Original sleeve No. 215
      Plate number: 747
    - Left-center section of panorama of Yale Bowl during Yale-Princeton game, 1920, 1919; 1 box (Box 38)
      Original sleeve No. 216
      Plate number: 748
    - Right-center section of panorama of Yale Bowl during Yale-Princeton game, 1921, 1919; 1 box (Box 38)
      Original sleeve No. 217
      Plate number: 749
    - Right section of panorama of Yale Bowl during Yale-Princeton game, 1922, 1919; 1 box (Box 38)
      Original sleeve No. 218
      Plate number: 750
    - First quarter of Yale-Princeton gae, 1919, 1 box (Box 38)
      Original sleeve No. 219
      Plate number: 751
    - Yale's First field goal in Yale-Princeton game, 1919, 1 box (Box 38)
      Original sleeve No. 220
      Plate number: 752
    - Princeton pushed out of bounds in least quarter of Yale-Princeton game, 1919, 1 box (Box 38)
      Original sleeve No. 221
      Plate number: 753
    - Princeton's second field goal in last quarter of Yale-Princeton game, 1919, 1 box (Box 38)
      Original sleeve No. 222
      Plate number: 754
    - Princeton snake dance on the field at the close of the Princeton-Yale game, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 223
      Plate number: 755
    - Freshman on the water wagon for the bonfire, November, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 224
      Plate number: 756
    - Unloading a carriage for the bonfire, November, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 225
      Plate number: 757
    - Freshman off for more wood for fire, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 226
      Plate number: 758
    - All kinds of wood for the fire, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 227
      Plate number: 759
    - En route to the fire, November, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 228
      Plate number: 760
    - Another contribution to the fire, Nov., 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 229
      Plate number: 761
    - On goes the water wagon, bonfire, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 230
      Plate number: 762
    - Some of the foundation of the pile for the bonfire, November, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 231
      Plate number: 763
    - All headed for the fire, Nov., 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 232
      Plate number: 764
    - The Yale dummy for the fire, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 233
      Plate number: 765
    - Starting to build the bonfire pile, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 234
      Plate number: 766
    - Birds-eye view of wood for the bonfire, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 235
      Plate number: 767
    - The bonfire pile nearly built, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 236
      Plate number: 768
    - Flash light of the pile just before it was lit. November, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 237
      Plate number: 769
    - Yale victory bonfire, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 238
      Plate number: 770
    - Ruins of a carriage among the flames, Yale bonfire, 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 239
      Plate number: 771
    - The start of the bonfire, Nov., 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 240
      Plate number: 772
    - Nassau Hall tower illuminated by the Yale victory bonfire, Nov., 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 241
      Plate number: 773
    - The library tower illuminated by the Yale victory bonfire, Nov., 1919, 1 box (Box 39)
      Original sleeve No. 242
      Plate number: 774
    - P.U. sports, Football 1908 Champions, 1 box (Box 61)
      Plate number: 1180-1181
    - P.U. sports, Football 1907 Champions, 1 box (Box 61)
      Plate number: 1182-1183
    - Football, Undated; 1 box (Box 63)
      Plate number: 1211-1213
    - Princeton football, Undated; 1 box (Box 63)
      Plate number: 1214
    - 1908 football squad, 1 box (Box 63)
      Plate number: 1219
    - Athletics, football with Syracuse, 1915; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1241
    - Athletics, football with Lafayette, Osbourne Field, 1915?, circa 1915; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1242
    - Athletics, football with Harvard, Palmer Stadium, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      in Daily Princetonian 11/8/15
      Plate number: 1243
    - Athletics, football with Rutgers, Rutgers quaterback tries to go through Princeton Center, Osbourne Field, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1244
    - Outdoor 1930 football team, 1 box (Box 93)
    - Men's football, 1934, 1 box (Box 93)
    - Men's football, 1922, 1 box (Box 93)
      Emulsion layer seperated
    - Men's football, circa 1900, 1 box (Box 93)
    - Men's football team, 1933, outdoor, 1 box (Box 93)
    - Men's football, 1897, 1 box (Box 93)
    - Men's football, 1934, indoors under arches, 1 box (Box 93)
    - Men's football, 1932, 1 box (Box 93)
    - Outdoor team shot, football, early helemts, circa 1894, 1 box (Box 95)
    - "Billy" Coursen, 1881, in appreciation of our Princeton football "scrubs" past, present, and future plaque, circa 1881; 1 box (Box 97)
  - General, 1905-1920; 10 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Princeton University athletic activities. These plates could not clearly be associated with other topics in this series.
    Some plates lack description and may be associated with topics descibed elsewhere in the Finding Aid.
    - Rush at Bonner-Marquand gym, circa 1905; 1 box (Box 17)
      Plate number: 324
    - Yale game special trains, November, 1920, 1 box (Box 31)
      Original sleeve No. 100
      Plate number: 631
    - Coach Clarke and Captain Bade, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1045
      Plate number: 1051
    - P.U. sports, Undated; 3 boxes (Box 60, Box 61, Box 62)
      Plate number: 1144-1162, 1179, 1184-1201, and 1210
    - No Description Available, Undated; 1 box (Box 60)
      Plate number: 1171-1177
    - No Description Available, Undated; 1 box (Box 63)
      Plate number: 1178
    - Athletics, hockey, 1914; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1245
    - Sports team posed on steps outside arched doorway, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Sports team posed, sitting and standing, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Golf team, seven players with clubs, Undated; 1 box (Box 100)
  - Gymnastics, 1919; 2 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture the Princeton University Gymnastics team.
    - Erskine White, 1921, tumbling. Gym team, 1919, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 126
      Plate number: 657
    - Cooper, 1921, on the horse, gym team, 1919, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 127
      Plate number: 658
    - P.U. gymnasts, Undated; 1 box (Box 62, Box 63)
      Plate number: 1163-1168 and 1202-1208
  - Soccer, 1919; 2 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture the Princeton University Soccer team.
    - Athletics, soccer, H.B. Hoskins, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1247
    - Athletics, soccer, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1248
    - Princeton-Cornell soccer game, Oct., 1919, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 124-125
      Plate number: 655-656
  - Tennis, 1912-1920; 2 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture Princeton University Tennis.
    - Athletics, tennis, G.M. Church (Princeton) driving back and R. Norris Williams (Harvard) courts near Guyot, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1249
    - Tennis courts in play, Undated; 1 box (Box 97)
  - Track and Field, 1912-1920; 13 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture Princeton University Track and Field activities.
    - Athletics, intramural team?, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
      Plate number: 251
    - Track, intramural team?, Undated; 1 box (Box 11)
      Plate number: 277
    - Princeton 4-mile relay team, 1919, 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 301. Foresman, McCulloch, Raymond, and Penfield
      Plate number: 796
    - B. Penfield 1921, running in spring track practice, 1919, 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 302
      Plate number: 797
    - V.L. Raymond 1919 and D.B. Foresman 1921 running in spring practice 1919, 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 303
      Plate number: 798
    - Jacobs 1921 running in spring track practice, 1919, 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 304
      Plate number: 799
    - Sid Stewart 1920 and Bill Wren 1921 starting a spring, spring of 1919, 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 305
      Plate number: 800
    - Ted Speers throwing hammer, spring of 1920 in practice, 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 306
      Plate number: 801
    - Chuck Carpenter 1921 throwing hammer, spring of 1920, 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 307
      Plate number: 802
    - Ted Speers 1921 throwing hammer in practice, 1920; 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 308
      Plate number: 803
    - Terrell, Murrey, Erdman, and Stevenson, practicing a start, spring of 1920., 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 309
      Plate number: 804
    - Alan Swede and Don Foresman running in practice, spring of 1920, 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 310
      Plate number: 805
    - Brown and Don Lourie practicing a sprint, spring of 1920, 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 311
      Plate number: 806
    - George Trowbridge hurdling in practice, spring of 1920, 1 box (Box 41)
      Original sleeve No. 312
      Plate number: 807
    - Click McCulloch 1921 running in practice, spring of 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 313
      Plate number: 808
    - Start of 4-mile relay race in Penn relays, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 314
      Plate number: 809
    - Third mile of four mile relay race, Penn relays, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 315
      Plate number: 810
    - Last mile of four mile relay race, Penn relays, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 316
      Plate number: 811
    - Nevil Rudd, Oxford finishing first in 20 mile relay race in Penn relays, breaking world's record for the distance, Undated; 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 317
      Plate number: 812
    - Heat of high hurdles in Penn relays, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 318. Bill Massey, Princeton 1922 on the right.
      Plate number: 813
    - Heat of high hurdles in Penn relays, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 319. Earl Thomson of Dartmouth the world's champion hurdler in the foreground.
      Plate number: 814
    - Heat of high hurdles in Penn relays, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 320. George Trowbridge next to left
      Plate number: 815
    - Final of high hurdles in the Penn relays, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 321. Left to right: Harrison Thomson, Walker Smith of Cornell, George Trowbridge, Earl Thomson of Darthmouth.
      Plate number: 816
    - Yale track meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 322. First heat of 100 yard dasy with R.E. Brown and Frank Murrey
      Plate number: 817
    - Yale track meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 323. Second heat of 100 yard dash with Clark 1920 and Don Looooourie 1922
      Plate number: 818
    - Final of hundred yard dash in Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 324. Brown and Clark of Princeton
      Plate number: 819
    - First heat of 220 yard dash in Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 325. Won by Brown Princet
      Plate number: 820
    - Second heat of 220 yard dash in Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 326. Won by Clark, Princeton
      Plate number: 821
    - Final of 220 yard dash in Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 42)
      Original sleeve No. 327. Won by Brown, Princeton
      Plate number: 822
    - Cox of Yale beating Stevenson of Princeton in quartrer mile run in Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 328
      Plate number: 823
    - Frank Murrey, Princeton beating O'Brien of Yale in half mile run, Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 329
      Plate number: 824
    - Start of half mile run, Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 330
      Plate number: 825
    - Start of mile run, Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 331
      Plate number: 826
    - Al Swede of Princeton winning mile run, Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 332
      Plate number: 827
    - Start of two mile run, Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 333
      Plate number: 828
    - Hilles of Yale winning two mile run in Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 334
      Plate number: 829
    - First heat of high hurdles in Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 335. With Erdman and Trowbridge
      Plate number: 830
    - Second heat of high hurdles in Yale meet with Massey and Huhn, 1920; 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 336
      Plate number: 831
    - Final heat of high hurdles in Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 337
      Plate number: 832
    - First heat of low hurdles in Yale meet, 1920 with Erdman, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 338
      Plate number: 833
    - Second heat of low hurdles in Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 339. With Buzby and Trowbridge
      Plate number: 834
    - Final heat of low hurdles in Yale meet with Erdman, Trowbridge and Massey, 1920; 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 340
      Plate number: 835
    - Ted Speers throwing the hammer in the Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 341
      Plate number: 836
    - Chas. Halsey putting the shot in the Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 342
      Plate number: 837
    - Dick Cleveland putting the shot in the Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 343
      Plate number: 838
    - Uebelacker 1921, 1920 high jumping in Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 344
      Plate number: 839
    - Broad jump in Yale meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 345
      Plate number: 840
    - Brown 1920 winning 100 yard dash in Caledonian game, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 346
      Plate number: 841
    - Finish of quarter mile run, Caledonian games, 1920, 1 box (Box 43)
      Original sleeve No. 347
      Plate number: 842
    - Start of half mile run, Caledonian games, 1920, 1 box (Box 44)
      Original sleeve No. 348
      Plate number: 843
    - Finish of half mile run, Caledonian games, 1920, 1 box (Box 44)
      Original sleeve No. 349
      Plate number: 844
    - Start of mile run, Caledonian games, 1920, 1 box (Box 44)
      Original sleeve No. 350
      Plate number: 845
    - Alan Swede 1922 winning two mile run in Caledonian games, 1920, 1 box (Box 44)
      Original sleeve No. 351
      Plate number: 846
    - Click McCulloch winning mile run in Caledonian games, 1920, 1 box (Box 44)
      Original sleeve No. 352
      Plate number: 847
    - Start of 20 mile run in Caledonian games, 1920, 1 box (Box 44)
      Original sleeve No. 353
      Plate number: 848
    - Low hurdles in the Caledonian games, 1920, 1 box (Box 44)
      Original sleeve No. 354
      Plate number: 849
    - Start of the first heat of hundred yeard dash in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 44)
      Original sleeve No. 355
      Plate number: 850
    - Start of second heat of hundred yard dash in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 44)
      Original sleeve No. 356
      Plate number: 851
    - Finish of final of hundred yard dash in Haravrd meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 44)
      Original sleeve No. 357
      Plate number: 852
    - Final of 220 yard run in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 44)
      Original sleeve No. 358
      Plate number: 853
    - Start of quarter mile run in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 359
      Plate number: 854
    - Bill Stevenson winning Harvard meet quarter mile run, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 360
      Plate number: 855
    - Start of half mile run in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 361
      Plate number: 856
    - Start of mile run, Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 362
      Plate number: 857
    - McCulloch 1921 winning the mile run in the Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 363
      Plate number: 858
    - Start of 2 mile run in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 364
      Plate number: 859
    - Third lap of two mile run in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 365
      Plate number: 860
    - Seventh lap of two mile run in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 366
      Plate number: 861
    - Al Swede winning two mile run in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 367
      Plate number: 862
    - Final heat of high hurdles in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 368
      Plate number: 863
    - Don Lourie broad jumping in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 369
      Plate number: 864
    - Don Lourie jumping 23' 1" in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 370
      Plate number: 865
    - Uebelacker 1921 broad jumping in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 371
      Plate number: 866
    - Tevis Huhn broad jumping in Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 372
      Plate number: 867
    - Harwood of Harvard winning pole vault, Harvard meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 373
      Plate number: 868
    - Final of 100-yard dash in intercollegiate meet, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 374
      Plate number: 869
    - First heat of 220-yard dash in intercollegiate, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 375
      Plate number: 870
    - Second heat of 220-yard dash in intercollegiates, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 376
      Plate number: 871
    - Final of 220 yard dash in intercollegiates, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 377
      Plate number: 872
    - Start of half mile run in intercollegiates, 1920, 1 box (Box 45)
      Original sleeve No. 378
      Plate number: 873
    - First lap of half mile run in intercollegiates, 1920, 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 379
      Plate number: 874